Lloyd: So now that you've finished
session one of unit one, it's
time to complete the relevant
section of the assessment booklet.
You can access the assessment booklet
by clicking on the assessment link,
which will then give you the option
to download and save that in a
suitable location on your computer.
Once you've done that, you can open your
assessment booklet, and you will see that
it looks like the document on the screen.
So read through the assessment guidance
and the key point here is to -- some
of the command verbs for some of
the questions is describe, explain,
identify, list define, state outline,
and it gives you a little bit of an idea
of what you should be thinking about
when you're answering those questions.
Try to provide as much detail as you
can if you are asked to describe or
explain as opposed to identify/list
where you can't just list your responses.
So the next thing to do is just
put your name at the top of page
two, and then you can move on.
You will have reference to the
learning objectives and which question
it relates to and where you can
find information relating to that
in the actual course materials.
If you're not sure.
So for question one "In the box
below, describe the term cyber crime".
So what is cyber crime?
This is a describe question
so try to provide as much
detail as you possibly can.
For question two, this
is an explain question.
So again, try and provide good
detail in your response, and
this is asking you to explain the
possible motives for cyber crime.
So what motivates cyber criminals?
What are the motives behind that?
And give three examples.
For question three, this is an identify
question, so you can list your responses.
So you need to identify the
potential threat actors.
So who is it that could be
carrying out the attack?
For question four, this question is
asking for a definition, so you need to
give a definition of what an external
threat is, and also an insider threat.
So what is an external threat,
what is an insider threat?
For question five, it's another describe
question, and it's asking you to describe
the possible motivations that could
lead to external and insider threats.
So what motivates people to carry out
those external or internal threats?
And for question six, it's asking
you to explain what is meant by
targeted and untargeted attacks.
So what is a targeted attack and
what is an untargeted attack?
So once you've done that, you
can then move on to session two.